High-Tech Sunglasses Fit Over Prescriptions!  

Call 1-800-618-5804

Privacy Policy  

Effective date: January 1st, 2021  

WE TAKE PRECAUTIONS WITH USER INFORMATION AND PERSONAL DATA. We value our  
users and respect your privacy.

This Website is operated by Telebrands Corp. (“we/our/us”). “You/your” means you as a user of the  
Website. “User” means all users of this Website. We offer this Website, including all information, tools  
and services available from this Website, to you conditioned upon your acceptance of all the terms,  
conditions, policies and notices stated here.

WE TAKE PRECAUTIONS WITH USER INFORMATION AND PERSONAL DATA. We value our  
users and respect your privacy. We collect information about you through the Website in an effort to  
fulfill orders for products, improve your online experience and to communicate with you about our  
products, services and promotions. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect  
about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. This Privacy Policy  
also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use certain of that information.

By accessing this Website, you acknowledge this Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by the terms  
hereof and the Terms of Use set forth on the Website. If there is anything you do not understand please  
write any inquiry to Telebrands Corp., 79 Two Bridges Road Fairfield, NJ 07004. If at any time you do  
not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website.

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy by posting such changes or updates to the  
Website. Amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when  
posted. It is your responsibility to review any such changes or updates and check the Website from time  
to time to be sure you understand all terms and conditions, agreements and policies of the Website and are  
in compliance with them. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the last modified date that  
appears at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of any  
amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

**OVERVIEW**  
Information about our data collection during the prior 12 months is described below.

You can access, delete and control certain uses of your information as set forth in the “Opt-Out” and  
“Rights to Your Information” sections below.

Categories of Personal  

Information

Contact information  

and other information  
about you such as your  
name, telephone  
number, email address  
and physical address  
and demographic  
information.

Financial information,  
product information,  
including credit card  
information

Online identifiers such  
as username, cookies,  
hashed email addresses,  
mobile device IDs  
including advertising  
identifiers, IP address,  
type of browser,  
operating system, date  
and time information  
and other technical  
information about your  
computer and browsing  
information.

Sources of such  
Personal Information

Collected from you  
directly through the  
Website or from your  
communications with  
us.

Collected from you  
directly when you  
purchase our products  
through the Website.

Collected by us when  
you visit our Website or  
interact with online  
advertisements, and  
from our partners who  
collect the information  
from you directly when  
you visit our partners’  
sites or use our partners’  
search engines.

Business Purpose for such Personal Information

We use such information  
to provide you our  
products and services,  
process and communicate  
with you about your  
orders, respond to  
inquiries we receive from  
you, send you marketing  
communications and as otherwise described in  
“Use of Your Personal  
Information” below.

We use such information  
to provide you our  
products and services,  
and process your orders.

We use such information  
to improve our Website  
and services, to deliver  
targeted advertising about  
goods and services that  
may be of interest to you,  
to assist anti-fraud  
services and as otherwise  
described in “Use of  
Your Personal  
Information” below.

Categories of Third Parties with whom information is shared

We share such  
information with  
our service  
providers and as  
otherwise described  
in “Sharing  
Personal  
Information With  
Third Parties” below.

We share such information with our service  
providers to process  
your order.

We share such  
information with  
our service  
providers, affiliates  
and advertising  
partners, sell this  
information to our  
customers and as  
otherwise described  
in “Sharing  
Personal  
Information With  
Third Parties”  
below.

\*As used in this Privacy Policy, “personal information” is information that directly or indirectly  

identifies a specific person, such as name, telephone number, physical address, or email address.

**1\. Information We Collect From You**  
We will ask you for certain kinds of personal information (“Personal Information”) to provide the  
services you request. This information includes:  
Ordering – When you place an order we ask for your name, address, phone number and email address.  
You may be required to provide credit card details. We will never share your credit card details with any  
other party except to process your order. By placing an order with us your information may be stored with  
us.  
Email List - When you place an order, you will be added to our email list. You will have the option to be  
removed from our email list by clicking the “unsubscribe” button found at the bottom of the emails we  
send you.  
Calls to Customer Service/Participation in Promotions/Sweepstakes or Surveys- If you call our Customer  
Service center or participate in one of our promotions or sweepstakes or user surveys, we may ask for  

additional information, such as your age, interests or product preferences.

**2\. Information We Collect Automatically or From Others**

2.1 Through your use of this Website, we may also collect certain information from you that does not  

directly identify you as an individual. It is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate.

2.2 The Website may use cookies. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved  
on your hard drive by your computer’s browser. Cookies help us remember you when you return to the  
Website. Cookies also hold information to personalize and enhance your experience and to gather website  
  
statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the Internet provider’s domain name and the addresses of  
the sites you visited immediately before coming to and immediately after leaving the Website. The  
information in the cookies lets us trace your “clickstream” activity (i.e., the paths taken by users of the  
Website as they move from page to page) to enable us to better serve our users by revealing which  
portions of the Website are the most popular. You may disable cookies on your browser. Please see the  

**“Opt-Out”** section below for more information on how to do so.

2.3 We may also use “pixel tags” (sometimes called “web beacons” or “clear gifs”), which are tiny  
graphic images, on the Website. Pixel tags help us analyze Users’ online behavior and measure the  
effectiveness of the Website and our advertising and marketing. We may also use other analytical tools to  
evaluate site performance through the use of aggregated data, which does not directly identify you. We  

work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

2.4 Cookies, pixel tags, and/or other analytical tools that we may use on the Website may collect  
information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and  
other actions you take in connection with the Website. This information may include your computer’s  
Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and  
other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the  
identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Website. We do not otherwise track  

any information about your use of other websites.

2.5 Cookies, pixel tags, and/or other analytical tools in our emails may be used to track your interactions  

with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.

2.6 We may also work with businesses that use tracking technologies to deliver advertisements on our  
behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to the Website and  

your interaction with our advertising and other communications.

2.7 We may combine the information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other analytical tools with  
other information we may have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our  
Website, to personalize your online experience, to help us deliver information to you, to determine the  

effectiveness of advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

2.8 We do not track users over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and  

therefore do not respond to Do Not Track signals.

**3\. Use of Your Personal Information**  
We use the Personal Information we collect for various purposes, including:  

* to complete your purchase transactions
* to provide the services you request
* to keep you informed about the status of your orders
* to identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products,
* services, and promotions that might be of interest to you
* to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased
* to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall Website experience
* to communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means
*   

**4\. Sharing Personal Information With Third Parties**  
4.1 We may share, sell or trade your Personal Information gathered online with third parties. We may  
contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to such Personal  

Information.

4.2 We may disclose your Personal Information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with law  
enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of  
the Website, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of  

Users of this Website or the public.

4.3 We may also disclose your Personal Information to outside individuals and/or companies that help us  
bring you the products and services we offer and to create, operate, and maintain our Website. For  
example, we may work with third parties to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist us  
in distributing e-mails; (c) assist us with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and  
analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service; (g) provide product fulfillment and  
shipping services; and (h) provide other services designed to assist us in developing and running our  
Website and maximizing our business potential. We require that these outside companies agree to keep all  
information shared with them confidential and to use the information only to perform their obligations to  

us.

4.4 In addition, if we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company,  
or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets  

transferred.

**5\. Sales of Information**  
We may sell your Personal Information to third parties, subject to your right to opt-out of those sales (See  
the _“Opt-Out”_ and _“Rights to Your Information”_ sections below).  
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have sold the categories of Personal Information in the chart set  

forth above.

**6\. Your Security**  
6.1 We strive to keep your Personal Information private and safe. We take commercially reasonable  
physical, electronic and administrative steps to maintain the security of Personal Information collected,  
including limiting the number of people who have physical access to database servers, as well as  
employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access.  
In addition, it is our policy to never send your credit card number via e-mail. Please note that e-mail is not  
encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information, so please do  

not send us your credit card number by email.

6.2 We use Secure Socket Layers (SSL), the industry standard in transferring information to process your  
orders. SSL encrypts, or translates, your order information into a highly indecipherable code, which is  
processed immediately. All credit card transactions occur in a secure area of the Website to protect you  
from any loss, misuse or alteration of information collected. When you have finished shopping and begin  
the checkout process, you will move into the secure area of the Website. Once you have entered, the page  
address (URL) will change from “http” to “https” to let you know you are in a secure area. Also, a key or  
a closed lock will appear in the lower right hand corner of your screen to notify you of this change. You  
will remain in this secure zone for the entire checkout process.  
  
6.3 Unfortunately, despite our best efforts, the transmission of data over the Internet cannot be guaranteed  
to be 100% secure. While we will use every reasonable means to ensure the security of information you  
transmit through the Website, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third  
parties. We will, however, prosecute any unauthorized or fraudulent transactions to the fullest extent  

permitted by law.

**7\. Links to Other Websites**  
7.1 While visiting the Website, you may link to websites operated by third parties or you may have come  
to the Website using a link found in another website. This does not mean that we endorse these websites  
or the goods or services they provide. We do not make any representations or warranties about any  
website that may be linked to the Website. Such other websites are independent from us, and we have no  

control over, or responsibility for, their information, products or activities.

7.2 In addition, our privacy practices may differ from those of these other websites. If you provide  
Personal Information at one of those websites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that  
website, not our Privacy Policy. Please make sure you understand the other website’s privacy policy  

before providing Personal Information.

**8\. Social Networking Services**  
The Website may integrate with social networking services. We do not control such services and are not  
liable for the manner in which they operate. While we may provide you with the ability to use such  
services in connection with our Website, we are doing so merely as an accommodation and, like you, are  

relying upon those third party services to operate properly and fairly.

You should be aware that Personal Information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a  
publicly accessible blog, social network or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others. We are  
unable to control such uses of your Personal Information, and by using such services you assume the risk  

that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

**9\. Opt-Out**  
You will receive promotional emails from us only if you have asked to receive them. If you do not want  
to receive e-mails from us you may click on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email  
communication sent by us. Please allow us 10 business days from when the request was received to  
complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted  

your request.

If you want to stop or restrict the placement of cookies or flush any cookies that may already be on your  
computer or device, please refer to and adjust your web browser preferences. Further information on  
cookies is available at www.allaboutcookies.org. By deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you  
may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Website or some of its functionality may be  
affected. Cookies and similar items are not used by us to automatically retrieve information that can  

identify you from your device without your knowledge.

**10\. Rights to Your Information**  
If you reside in California, under CCPA or applicable law, you have specific rights regarding your  
Personal Information. This section describes the rights that you have under CCPA, or other state laws as  

applicable, and explains how to exercise those rights.

**\*_Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed or Sold._** You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection, use, disclosure or sale of your Personal Information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable  
consumer request (see “_Exercising Access, and Deletion Rights_” below), and subject to certain  
limitations that we describe below, we will disclose such information to you. You have the right  

to request any or all of the following:

*  The categories of Personal Information we collected about you.
*  The categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected.
*  Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that Personal Information.
*  The categories of third parties with whom we share that Personal Information.
*  The specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you

**\* _Right to Request Deletion_.** You have the right to request that we delete any of your Personal  
Information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we  
receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see “_Exercising Access, and Deletion  
Rights”_ below), we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your Personal  
Information from our records. However, we may retain Personal Information that has been de-  
identified or aggregated. Furthermore, we may deny your deletion request if retaining the  
information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) in order to perform certain actions set  
forth under CCPA, such as detecting security incidents and protecting against fraud or illegal  

activity.

\***_Exercising Access and Deletion Rights._** To exercise the access and deletion rights described above, please submit a request to us by:  
  
Emailing us at privacy@telebrands.com  
  
Only you, or a person or business entity registered with the California Secretary of State that you  
authorize to act on your behalf (an “authorized agent”), may make the requests set forth above.  

You may also make a request on behalf of your minor child.

The request should include your contact information and describe your request with sufficient  
detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. In addition, you should  
provide sufficient information (including your full name, address, phone number, email address,  
order date, order number, product ordered) that allows us to reasonably verify that you are the  

person about whom we collected the personal information or an authorized representative.

We will respond to consumer requests in a reasonably timely manner. If we require extra time to  

respond, we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.

In order to protect the security of your Personal Information, we will not honor a request if we  
cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information  
relates to you. The method used to verify your identity will vary depending on the nature of the  
request. Generally speaking, verification will be performed by matching the identifying  

information provided by you to the Personal Information that we already have.

Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your  
request. We are not obligated to provide the information set forth above under “_Right to Know  
About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed or Sold_” more than twice in a 12-month  
period.  
  
We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is  
excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we  
will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing  

your request.

**\*_Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In Rights_.** You have the right to direct us to not sell  
your personal information at any time (the &quot;right to opt-out&quot;). We do not sell the personal  
information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age, unless we receive  
affirmative authorization (the &quot;right to opt-in&quot;) from either the consumer who is at least 13 and  

less than 16 years of age, or the parent or guardian of a consumer less than 13 years of age.

To exercise the right to opt-out, you (or your authorized representative) may submit a request to  

us by visiting the following Internet Web page: [Do Not Sell My Personal Information](https://www.telebrandsoptout.com/)

Alternatively, you may submit an opt-out request by emailing us at privacy@telebrands.com.

_**\*Non-Discrimination.**_ We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA  
rights, including, but not limited to, by:  

*  Denying you goods or services.
*  Charging you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
*  Providing you a different level or quality of goods or services.
*  Suggesting that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

**  
11\. “Spoofing” And “Phishing”**  
A common Internet scam is known as “spoofing” or “phishing.” This occurs when you receive an email  
from what appears to be a legitimate source requesting Personal Information from you. Please be aware  
that we will not send you any emails requesting you to verify credit card, bank information, or any other  
Personal Information. If you ever receive an email that appears to be from us requesting such information  

from you, DO NOT respond to it, and DO NOT click on any links appearing in the email.

**12\. Children and Privacy**  
The Website is not meant for children, and we will not knowingly collect any Personal Information from  
children under the age of 13 without verified parental consent. We will remove from our files any  
Personal Information of anyone we discover to be under 13 years old. Our online contests or sweepstakes  
are restricted to entrants who are at least 18 years old. We are concerned about the safety of children  
when they use the Internet, and we understand that children may not understand all the provisions of our  
Privacy Policy or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the  

Website.

**13\. Your California Privacy Rights**  
Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a  
notice describing what categories of Personal Information we share with third parties or corporate  
affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify  
the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it  
was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy  
of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Telebrands Corp., 79 Two Bridges  

Road Fairfield, NJ 07004. Please allow 30 days for a response.

**14\. Disclosure for Legal Purposes**  
You hereby authorize us to disclose any of your Personal Information pursuant to judicial and  
administrative proceedings and to law enforcement or government agencies if we believe the disclosure is  
necessary or appropriate. You also authorize us to disclose Personal Information if we believe the  
disclosure is necessary or appropriate in the event of an investigation of improper or illegal conduct in  
connection with the Website, such as fraud, misrepresentation, intellectual property infringement, or other  

activity that may put us at risk for liability.

**15\. Non-Confidential Information**  
We do not want you to send to us any confidential or proprietary information through email or otherwise.  
Any information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments sent to us will be considered non-  
confidential, and by submitting the same to us, you are giving us the absolute right to use, modify,  
reproduce, transmit, display and distribute the information for any purpose whatsoever, with no payment  
or other compensation to you. However, we will not use your name unless we are required by law to  
identify the source of the materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments, or unless we first obtain  

your permission.

**16\. Assignment**  

We may freely assign this Privacy Policy or any of our rights and/or obligations hereunder.

**17\. Contact**  
If you have any questions about your privacy or security at the Website, please write to Telebrands Corp.,  
79 Two Bridges Road Fairfield, NJ 07004 and include your name, address and email address in the  
message. If you do not receive a response from us within 30 days, please send us another letter as your  
original correspondence may not have been received.

Copyright © 2024 DaVinci CSJ, LLC
